babyage.com 2009-12-08

# Security And Privacy - Help Desk - BabyAge.com

Customer Service

**Phone** : 1-800-BABYAGE

**Fax** : 1-570-706-2459

**Online Customer Support** : Click Here

**Business Hours** :   
Monday through Friday, 9:00AM - 7:00PM Eastern Time  
**Customer Service Hours** :   
Monday through Friday, 9:00AM - 3:00AM Eastern Time  
Saturday, 9:00AM - 9:00PM Eastern Time  
Sunday, 12:00PM - 9:00PM Eastern Time

| 

### Security & Privacy

#### SECURE SHOPPING SITE

We take the security of your online transactions seriously. Your credit card information is protected by state-of-the-art encryption software. The encryption process makes your online ordering safe; it is the standard for processing a secure credit card order over the Internet.

### PRIVACY POLICY

At BabyAge.com, we are fully aware of the concerns about personal privacy on the Internet. We have created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. What follows is the BabyAge.com corporate philosophy information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site:

BabyAge.com employs data-acquisition practices that provide our clients with value and that foster the level of trust among consumers that is necessary to grow long-term value relationships. It is completely your decision how much personally identifiable information you choose to disclose to BabyAge.com. The only way we know something about you personally is if you provide that information in one of the surveys, registrations or other marketing activities we hold from time to time. If, however, you choose to interact with BabyAge.com, you have our guarantee of privacy: We do not sell or rent information about our customers at any cost. BabyAge.com uses personally identifying data, provided by you, our customers, only in connection with our use of the BabyAge.com site and for BabyAge.com promotion, planning and inventory purposes and will not disseminate it to parties outside of BabyAge.com. All information provided to BabyAge.com remains confidential. BabyAge.com will never willfully disclose personally identifiable information about you to any third party without receiving your permission.

#### Information Automatically Logged

We use your IP address and browser type to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is also used to gather broad demographic information.

#### Cookies

Our Site uses cookies to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly. We also use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, and to analyze what customers like and don't like about our offerings so we can provide better service.

#### Personal Information 

It is completely your decision how much personally identifiable information you choose to disclose to BabyAge.com. Unless you specifically tell us, BabyAge.com will never know who you are, even though we have assigned your computer a cookie. If, however, you choose to interact with BabyAge.com, you have our guarantee of privacy: BabyAge.com will never willfully disclose personally identifiable information about you to any third party without receiving your permission.

#### Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can call or email us.

#### Opting out from BabyAge.com Communications

From time to time, you may receive telephone calls, periodic mailings or e-mails from BabyAge.com Team members with information on products or services, discounts, special promotions, upcoming events or other Babyage.com offers or marketing partner offers. You may opt out of receiving e-mail communications by clicking the "Unsubscribe" link at the bottom of the e-mail received. It may take us up to 10 days to complete this process, as permitted by law. You may opt out of receiving mailings or telephone calls by calling 1-800-BABYAGE and requesting to be removed.

#### Site Links

The BabyAge.com Site may contain links to other sites, including content from other sites that is occasionally framed within the BabyAge.com site. Please note that the privacy policies at these other sites may be different from this one. You should review the privacy policy of any site linked to or framed within the BabyAge.com Site prior to providing any information on or to that site.

#### Contact BabyAge.com

If you have questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please [Click Here](http://www.babyage.com/customersupport.aspx) to send an e-mail via our Customer Support Form or call 1-800-BABYAGE.

» Back to Help
